Guide to the Women's Center records, 1970-2005, bulk 1983-2005 UA.09.17.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Women's Center records
1970-2005, bulk 1983-2005
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University. Women's Center
UA.09.17.0001
21 Linear Feet
6.46 Megabytes
The Women's Center serves the Duke undergraduate, graduate and professional student communities. The center supports and promotes student women and gender issues on campus. Materials present include subject files, correspondence, memoranda, reports, proposals, surveys, programming records, committee records, flyers, job descriptions, training materials, photographs, slides, videocassettes, and other materials relating to the history and daily operation of the Center.
about 21,000 Items
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
Electronic records in this collection have been migrated to a library server and digital use copies can only be accessed onsite in the Rubenstein Library Reading Room. To request access, please contact Research Services before coming to use these records.
For a period of twenty-five years from the origin of the material, permission in writing from the office of origin and the University Archivist is required for use. After twenty-five years, records that have been processed may be consulted with the permission of the University Archivist.
Provenance
The Women's Center records were received by the University Archives as transfers in 1993-2008.
Historical Note
The Women's Center serves the Duke undergraduate, graduate and professional student communities. The Center was established in January of 1989 and began offering programming in the fall of 1989 after a two and a half year process begun by a group of undergraduate women who called themselves "The Coalition for a Women's Center at Duke." The Coalition researched and published a report outlining the need for a Center whose sole purpose was to support and promote student women and gender issues on campus. A task force was appointed by the Vice President for Student Affairs and its charge was to further research the need for and explore the feasibility of a Women's Center at Duke. After being founded, the Women's Center expanded its services to include the Office of Sexual Assault Support Services (SASS) in the spring of 1991.
The Women's Center is a department within the Division of Student Affairs and part of the Campus Life management team within the Division. The Women's Center's Director reports to the Assistant Vice-President for Student Affairs. The Women's Center's budget comes from the Division of Student Affairs. The SASS budget comes from Student Health fees. The Women's Center is currently (2008) staffed by 5 professional staff members: a Director, a Program Coordinator, an Office Manager, the Coordinator of Sexual Assault Support Services, and an Assistant Coordinator of Sexual Assault Support Services. Directors include: Martha Stewart, 1989-1993; Ellen Plummer, 1993-1998; Donna Lisker, 1999-2007; and Ada Gregory.
Collection Overview
The Women's Center records contain subject files, correspondence, memoranda, reports, proposals, surveys, programming records, committee records, flyers, job descriptions, training materials, photographs, slides, videocassettes, and other materials relating to the history and daily operation of the Center. Major subjects include sexual assault, crime prevention, safe sex, gender issues, sorority life, harassment, and women in science and engineering. Materials can also be found on the following groups or programs: BASES (Building Awareness through Shared Experiences); DARE (Duke Acquaintance Rape Education); GWPN (Graduate and Professional Women's Network); MAC (Men Acting for Change); SASS (Sexual Assault Support Services); Take Back the Night; VOICES (magazine published by the Women's Center); WISE (Women in Science and Engineering); Women of Color; and the Women's Center Art Gallery. Materials range in date from 1983-2005.
Separated Material
Several 3.5 floppy discs were removed from acession A2002-68 containing Building Awareness through Shared Experience (BASE) files. These discs have not been processed as of July 2009. Further evaluation in consultation with the Electronic Records Archivist will be required for use. Four T-120 VHS videocassettes were removed from accession A2006-0047; three contain Duke Acquaintance Rape Education (DARE) material and the final contains an interview with Seldon Holt and Amy Ellison on the filming of "Kiss the Girls" which aired on Fox 22 News in 1996. One 5.25" floppy was removed from A2006-0047 containg material relating to the spring 1992 mock trial titled "Date Rape on Trial."
Related Material
Baldwin Scholars Program records, 2003-2007
University Archives/David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Division of Student Affairs reference collection, 1987-[ongoing]
University Archives/David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Women’s Network Records, 1975-1988
University Archives/David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Women’s Studies Program records, circa 1973-2004
University Archives/ David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Women’s Studies Reference Collection, 1988-[ongoing]
University Archives/David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Voices [serial] 1993-[ongoing]
University Archives/David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Women college students -- Services for -- North Carolina—Durham; Women’s rights; Women -- Violence against; Women college administrators -- North Carolina -- Durham; Family Violence -- North Carolina -- Durham; Minority college students; Acquaintance rape -- Prevention -- North Carolina -- Durham; Feminism; Duke University. Women’s Center; Duke University. Division of Student Affairs; Women in higher education -- North Carolina -- Durham
- A99-3, 1986-1996, 4.5 boxes
  Scope and Contents note
  Accession contains correspondence, reports, proposals, surveys, programming records, committee records, and other materials with inclusive dates 1986-1996. Some files concern Judicial Board matters and are restricted. Major subjects/programs present include Task Force on a Duke University Women's Center, Men Acting for Change, campus climate, sexual harassment, Women of Color, and Student Affairs.
  - Advisory Board Binder, 1989-1991, 4 folders (Box 1)
  - Women's Center Duke - Historical Documents, 1987-1989 (Box 1)
  - Proposal Draft #3 [includes results from college and university women's center survey and proposal for the Sarah Doyle Center at Brown University] (Box 1)
  - Proposal Final Draft, 1986-1987 [Task Force on a Duke University Women's Center] (Box 1)
  - Anecdotes, 1986 ["Why Duke needs a Women's Center" for proposal] (Box 1)
  - Task Force Proposal, 1986 (Administration Interviews Student Affairs) (Box 1)
  - Women's Center, Goals and Objectives 1990-1993, 1989 [includes Director's Report, 1989] (Box 1)
  - Workshop - Starting a Women's Center, NWSA, 1990 [good historical Duke Women's Center information] (Box 1)
  - Student Programming Council, 1989-1990 (Box 1)
  - Multiculturalism Task Force Meeting, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Leadership Research 1989-1990 Project, C. Pearcy, 1989-1990, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Maternity Leave Policy, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Undergraduate Enrollment Report, Evans Report, 1990-1991 (Box 1)
  - Political Correctness Debate, Sept. 1991 (Box 1)
  - Committee on Social Alternatives, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Administration Women's Network Advocacy Project, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Campus Climate Survey: Faculty Comments, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Campus Climate Surveys, 1989-1991 (Box 1)
  - Survey Drafts, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Student Surveys, Examples (Box 1)
  - Staff Surveys, Examples (Box 1)
  - Men's Resource Initiative Consortium, 1992 [M1] (Box 1)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Central Campus Housing, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Marketing Plan, 1990-1991 (Box 1)
  - Women's Center Brochure, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
  - Women's Center Sign, 1993-1994 (Box 1)
  - Richard Whitted Leadership Workshop, undated (Box 1)
  - Director's Report, January/February 1991 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report: Victoria, Summer 1990 (Box 1)
  - Events, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Women's History Month, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Goals 1989-1990 (May 1989, Bill Griffith) (Box 1)
  - Programming, August/September 1989 (Box 1)
  - Programming, October 1989 (Box 1)
  - Proposal: Experiential Feminism Class, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Soviet Women's Visit, October 1989 [photographs] (Box 1)
  - Playboy, October 1989 (Box 1)
  - Playboy petitions, copies (Box 1)
  - Program for Administration Women's Network, October 1989 (Box 1)
  - MALS [Master of Arts in Liberal Studies] Panel, October 20, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Chris Williamson/Theresa Trull [concert], October 21, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Alcohol Conference, October 31- November 1, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Katherine Kolbert, November 2, 1989 [ACLU Lawyer, visit and lecture] (Box 1)
  - Programming, November 1989 (Box 1)
  - Planning Office, November 1989/Accompanying Narrative (Box 1)
  - Graduate and Professional School Women Lunch, November 6, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Montreal murders, December 1989 (Box 1)
  - Jabberwocky Controversy, 1989-1990 (Box 1)
  - Sexual Decision Making, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Dr. Susannah Heschel, February 12-13, 1990 [scholar in residence] (Box 1)
  - Dr. Lenora Felani, February 19, 1990 [speaker] (Box 1)
  - Feminist Theory Lectures - February/March 1990 (Box 2)
  - Publicity- Spring Events, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Women's Career Luncheon, March 31, 1991 (Box 2)
  - Women's Spirituality Meetings, 1990-1991 (Box 2)
  - Women's Center Scrapbook, 1989-1990 (Box 2)
  - Duke Life 202, and 303, 1991 (Box 2)
  - Luncheon, March 1990 [Career Exploration Luncheon for Duke Women] (Box 2)
  - Women's Center Move, August 1991 [Photographs] (Box 2)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 2)
  - Career Exploration Luncheon foe Duke Women, Fall 1990 (Box 2)
  - Beijing Conference, June 26-30, 1990 (Box 2)
  - National Women's Studies Association (NWSA) Conference Workshop "Starting a Women's Center" June 20-24, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, 1989-1991 [Martha Simmons] (Box 2)
  - Events 1990-1991 (Box 2)
  - Safety Skills Training - ASDU Sponsored, Fall 1990 (Box 2)
  - "Celebration of Our Work" November 2-3, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Administrative Women's Network, October 22, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Joan Baez, Page Auditorium, November 24, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Gender and Food Group, Fall 1990 (Box 2)
  - Stress Relief Sessions, December 1990 (Box 2)
  - ACE (American Council on Education) project, "New Agenda of Women," Spring 1991 (Box 2)
  - Mentoring Program: 1991 Heather Heckel/Seldon Holt (Box 2)
  - Jean Kilborne, "Marketing Misery: Selling Addictions to Women, "February 25, 1991 (Box 2)
  - Jean Kilbourne, Funding Responses, 1990-1991 (Box 2)
  - Michael Kimmel, February 12, 1991 (Box 2)
  - Lesbian and Gay Awareness Week, February 9-16, 1991 (Box 2)
  - Madeline L'Engle, April 9-10, 1991 (Box 2)
  - Will Keim, May 1991 (Box 2)
  - Events 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - Final Four Celebration, 1992 (Box 2)
  - Dr. Rustomje Kerns, 1991 [scholar of South Asian-American Women writers]
    - December 2 lecture (Box 2)
    - December 3 workshop (Box 2)
  - Student Leadership Workshop, April 23, 1992 (Box 2)
  - Open Houses, Spring 1992 (Box 2)
  - Spring Lunch Series, 1992, 1989-1992 [opportunity for students to informally meet successful women to talk about balancing career and personal life] (Box 2)
  - Flyers/Brochures/Events, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - Women's Outreach Day, September 26, 1992 (Box 2)
  - Mary Rowe visit, January 28-29, 1992 [consult on Duke's Harassment Policies] (Box 2)
  - Sexual Harassment workshop with English Dept., spring 1992 (Box 2)
  - Events 1992-1995, 3 folders (Box 2)
  - Men Acting for Change (MAC), 1992-1993, 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Men Acting for Change (MAC), roster, undated (Box 2)
  - Men Acting for Change (MAC), 1992 [slides and visual material for slideshow "What's so sexy about pornography?"], 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Laura X [speaker on marital rape] (Box 2)
  - Unfoldered material from binder [miscellaneous flyers, photographs, articles], 4 folders (Box 2)
  - Take Bake the Night, 1987-1989 (Box 2)
  - Women's Center Volunteer and Staff Lists, 1992-1995 (Box 2)
  - Lesbian/Bisexual Women, 1992 (Beth Ann Koelsch) (Box 2)
  - Career/Mentoring Lunches Series, 1990-1993 (Mentor name lists) (Box 2)
  - Runner's Network, 1993-1994 (Box 2)
  - Issue Lunches, 1993-1994 (Laura Rosenstein, Anne DePrice) (Box 2)
  - Women's Center Art Gallery, 1993-1994 (Box 2)
  - BASES, 1994-1996 (Box 2)
  - Practical Workshops, 1995 (Box 3)
  - Women's Center programs, 1992-1994 (Box 3)
  - Women of Color 1991-1992 (coordinator Tonya Robinson) (Box 3)
  - Women of Color, 1992-1993 (coordinator Celia Naylor-Ojurongbe) (Box 3)
  - In the Spirit: Women of Color 1992-1993 (Box 3)
  - Women of Color, 1993-1994 (coordinator Tiffany Speaks) (Box 3)
  - Duke-Frontiers of Legal Thought, January 25-27, 1990 [conference] (Box 3)
  - National Coalition against Domestic Violence, 1987 (Box 3)
  - North Carolina Coalition against Domestic Violence (Box 3)
  - North Carolina on the Status of Women, 1989 (Box 3)
  - National Women's Studies Association (Box 3)
  - National Council for Research on Women (Box 3)
  - National Association of Women's Centers, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Duke Students for Choice (Box 3)
  - Project WILD, Body Image and Stereotyping (Box 3)
  - Global Nomads (Box 3)
  - Women in Engineering (Box 3)
  - Women's Law Society, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Divinity School Women's Center, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Statistics-Women and Men at Duke University, 1988-1991 (Box 3)
  - Campus Climate - Women's Studies Report, Duke 1987 (Box 3)
  - Duke Gender Picture-General, 1988 (Box 3)
  - Misogynist Miscellaneous Information, undated (Box 3)
  - Photos [University Photo Files] - Gender Balanced (Box 3)
  - Duke Matriculant Study, 1985-1989 (Box 3)
  - Biology-Zoology (BoZo) Survey, 1989-1990 (Box 3)
  - Duke - Gender, 1990 [Distinguished Professorships] (Box 3)
  - Religion Dept. 1989 (Box 3)
  - Epsilon Sigma Alpha, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Graduate and Professional Student Network, 1989-1993 (Box 3)
  - Retention Study - Duke Engineering, 1990-1991 (Box 3)
  - East Campus for 1st Year Students, 1990-1993 (Box 3)
  - Resident Advisors workshops - Group facilitation, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Residential Life Programming, 1989-1993 (Box 3)
  - Experimental Living/Learning Endowment, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Draft Policy-Sexual Harassment, April 7, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Non-Discrimination Policy, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Black Women Alumni Directory (Box 3)
  - Backlash, 1990 and undated [topics present: conservative student groups; Twin Peaks posters; Anti-Semitism] (Box 3)
  - Women's Center Advisory Board Meetings, 1989; 1991 (Box 3)
  - Duke Experience Survey Class of 1988 (Box 3)
  - Duke Admissions Materials-Gender Analysis, undated (Box 3)
  - Center for Creative Learning, 1988-1989 (Box 3)
  - Women Housing on West, 1992-1993 (Box 3)
  - Duke's Vision
    - Duke's Vision, 1990-1991 (Box 3)
    - Process Papers, 1989-1991 (Box 3)
    - Ongoing Meetings, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Women Studies at Duke-Materials, 1989-1992 (Box 3)
  - House Courses, 1989-1993 (Box 3)
  - Student Affairs Strategic Planning, 1992-1993 (Box 3)
  - Student Affairs Staff Meetings, 1989-1991 (Box 3)
  - National Academy of Scholars (NAS), 1990 (Box 3)
  - Student Affairs Trustee Committee Meeting, December 8, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Duke Experience Survey, Class of 1988 (Box 3)
  - The Campus climate Revisited: Chilly for Women Faculty, Administrators, and Graduate Students, October 1986 (Box 3)
  - Chilly Papers Collection, 1982-1989 [Project on the status and education of women: published by the Association of American Colleges] (Box 3)
  - Diversity, 1989-1991 (Box 3)
  - ESTEEM Program, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Community Service Center Board's Information, 1993-1994, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Sexual Harassment Task Force, 1993, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Safety Task Force, 1992-1993, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Staff, 1993-1994 [includes staff meeting notes and staff reports], 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, 1993-1994 [Ellen Plummer] (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, 1994-1995 [Ellen Plummer] (Box 4)
  - Women Center Staff, students, 1994-1995 (Box 4)
  - Meetings with Janet, 1993-1994 [Ellen Plummer/Janet Dickerson] (Box 4)
  - Budgets, 1994-1995 (Box 4)
  - Student Affairs - Performance Appraisal Subcommittee, 1993-1994 (Box 4)
  - Nan Keohane, 1992-1994, 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Student Affairs Strategic Planning Committee, 1992 (Box 4)
  - Student Affairs Retreat, June 1992 (Box 4)
  - Provost - John Strohbehn, October 13, 1994 (Box 4)
  - Division [Student Affairs] Staff Meetings, 1993-1994 (Box 4)
  - Development-Student Affairs friends, 1994 (Box 4)
  - Student Affairs Staff Development/Enhancement Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 4)
  - Trustees-Student Affairs Committee "Women's Issues" presentation with Women's Studies, December 10, 1993 (Box 4)
  - Student Affairs-Strategic Plan, 1993 (Box 4)
  - Women's Studies, UNC-CH (Box 4)
  - Durham County, Women's Commission, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Administrative Panel Proceedings, 1989-1990
    Conditions Governing Access note
    The following three folders containing Administrative Panel Proceedings material are closed for a period of twenty-five years from date of origination.
    - Judicial Hearing - Sigma Phi Epsilon, November 1990, 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Administrative Hearing, 1990 (Box 4)
    - Administrative Panel Proceedings, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Women's Center Management Sessions with Barb Briner, Fall 1992 (Box 4)
  - Summary List Activities, Fall 1991 (Box 4)
  - Staff Reports [re: programming and activities]
    - September 1991 (Box 4)
    - October 1991 (Box 4)
    - November 1991 (Box 4)
    - December 1991 (Box 4)
    - January 1992 (Box 4)
    - February 1992 (Box 4)
    - March, 1992 (Box 4)
    - April 1992 (Box 4)
    - September-October 1992 (Box 4)
    - November 1992 (Box 4)
    - January 1993 (Box 4)
    - February 1993 (Box 4)
    - March 1993 (Box 4)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education (COFHE), 1986-1991
    - COFHE, 1985; 1987 (Box 4)
    - COFHE Project, 1991 (Box 4)
  - ACE Survey, 1990 [Cooperative Institutional Research Program Freshman Survey Institutional Summary] (Box 4)
  - Long Range Planning, Advisory Committee on Resources-Response, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Admitted Student Questionnaire (Highlights and detailed reports) Duke University, 1991, 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Women's Studies/Women's Center regular meeting notes, 1989-1990, undated (Box 4)
  - Annual Report Materials, 1990-1991 (Box 4)
  - Descriptive Narrative of the Women's Center, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Budget Programming Summary, 1990-1991 (Box 4)
  - Harvard Conference, "Women and Men on Campus," 1991 (Box 4)
  - Women's Center Office Orientation, 1991 (Box 4)
  - Studio '91 (Theater/Production), 1991 (Box 4)
  - Response to inquiries on Women's Center, Spring 1992 (Box 4)
  - Miscellaneous Material, 1988-1992 (Box 4)
  - Abortion, local services (brochures), undated (Box 5)
  - Abortion, University activism, 1989-1993 (Box 5)
  - Athletics, Manual for Women Athletes, 1990-1992 (Box 5)
  - National Association for Girls and Women in Sports, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Women's Businesses
    - local directory, 1992-1993 (Box 5)
    - Ladyslipper, 1993 (Box 5)
    - Southern Sisters, 1989-1990 (Box 5)
  - Chilly Papers
    - Chilly Papers, undated (Box 5)
    - Ten years later, 1990, 1992 (Box 5)
    - Out of the Classroom, Campus Climate, undated (Box 5)
  - Campus Climate
    - Minority Students, 1988-1992, 2 folders (Box 5)
    - "Minorities on Campus," pamphlets, 1991 (Box 5)
    - Campus Climate for Women Faculty, Administrators, and Graduate Students, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Campus Violence, 1988-1991 (Box 5)
  - Strategies to Combat Campus Violence (NWSA Pre-Conference, Women's Center Caucus), 1989 July (Box 5)
  - Domestic Violence/Battering, undated (Box 5)
  - Gender Balancing the Police: Stopping Violence Against Women, 1991 (Box 5)
  - National Coalition against Domestic Violence (NCADV), 1990 (Box 5)
  - Orange/Durham Coalition for Battered Women, 1990 (Box 5)
  - North Carolina Coalition against Domestic Violence, 1990-1991 (Box 5)
  - Violence against Women, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Violence against Women, bibliographies, 1994 (Box 5)
- A2001-42, 1983-1999, bulk 1989-1999, 3 boxes
  Accession contains correspondence, memoranda, reports, programming evaluations, and other print materials with inclusive dates 1983-1999, bulk 1989-1999. Major subjects include 10th anniversary plans, the Graduate and Professional Women's Network (GWPN), programming, gender issues, harassment, and VOICES magazine.
  - Spring 1999 (Box 5)
    - Woman's Center 10-Year Anniversary, 1999 (Box 5)
    - Graduate and Professional Women's Network (GPWN), Spring 1998 (Box 5)
    - GPWN Programming, 1997-1998 (Box 5)
  - Fall 1997
    - "Financial Planning" [GPWN Program]
      - Evaluations, 1997 (Box 5)
    - "Breaking the Glass Ceiling" [GPWN Program]
      - Evaluations, 1997 (Box 5)
    - "Racism and Mental Health" [GPWN Program]
      - Evaluations, 1997 (Box 5)
    - "Harassment Prevention" [GPWN Program]
      - Evaluations and Handouts, 1997 (Box 5)
    - "Balancing Family and Career" [GPWN Program]
      - Evaluations, 1997 (Box 5)
    - "Meyer's Briggs" [GPWN Program]
      - Evaluations, 1997 (Box 5)
    - "Car Repair," Saturday [GPWN Program]
      - Evaluations, 1997 (Box 5)
    - Habitat Saturday, 1997 (Box 5)
    - Race/Gender/Sexuality, Small Group, 1997 [GPWN Program] (Box 5)
    - Race/Gender/Class/Sex Orientation Discussion Group, 1997 (Box 5)
    - GPWN Advertising Information, 1997 (Box 5)
    - GPWN Summer Planning, 1997 (Box 5)
  - Summer 1997
    - "If I Knew Then…"
      - Evaluations, 1997 (Box 5)
    - "Working…Social Change" [GPWN Program]
      - Evaluations, 1997 (Box 5)
    - "Mothers/Daughter Struggles and Celebrations," [GPWN Program]
      - Evaluations, 1997 (Box 5)
    - Movie: "Antonia's Line," 1997 [GPWN Program] (Box 5)
    - Book Discussion: The Woman Who Walked Into Doors ~ Domestic Violence, 1997 [GPWN Program] (Box 5)
    - Surveys: Women with Children/Non-traditional age (Box 5)
    - GPWN Summer Planning, 1997 (Box 5)
  - Spring 1997
    - Stress Reduction, 1997 [GPWN Program] (Box 5)
    - Shifting Social Roles, 1997 (Box 5)
    - GPWN Spring Scheduling, 1997 (Box 5)
    - Spring 1997 [GPWN Programs] (Box 5)
  - Year-End 1996-1997
    - Survey Results, 1996-1997 [Survey of GPWN Programs] (Box 5)
    - Year End Evaluations GPWN, 1996-1997 (Box 5)
    - Annual Report, 1996-1997 (Box 5)
    - GPWN Evaluation, 1997 (Box 5)
  - GPWN Fall Schedule Information, 1996 (Box 5)
  - Summer 1996
    - Diversity and Unity among Women at Duke: Finding Common Ground (Box 5)
    - Fall Flyers, 1996, 6 digital files in Quark Express Data format; approximately 0.34 megabytes. (Box 5)
      Digital files consist of event flyers created in Quark Express desktop publishing environment.
      Conditions Governing Access
      Electronic records in this series have been migrated to a library server and digital use copies can only be accessed onsite in the Rubenstein Library Reading Room. To request access, please contact Research Services before coming to use these records.
    - Year-End GPWN Evaluations, 1995-1996 (Box 5)
  - Spring 1996
    - GPWN Directory (Box 5)
    - GPWN Spring Schedule (Box 5)
  - GPWN Orientation and Mentoring 1997
    - Graduate School Orientation, 1996 (Box 5)
    - Steering Committee, 1997 (Box 5)
    - GPWN Orientation, 1997 (Box 5)
    - GPWN: Orientation
      - Survey Evaluation, 1997 (Box 5)
    - GPWN Connection, Fall 1997 (Box 5)
  - GPWN Mentoring 1996
    - GPWN Mentoring Program, 1996 (Box 5)
    - Mentoring Survey Results (Box 5)
    - Housing and Mentors, 1996 (Box 5)